homeschoolingmom4two.com 2013-03-27

# Homeschooling Mom 4 Two: Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy (last update: Oct 2012)  
  
**Privacy Policy for:  <http://homeschoolingmom4two.blogspot.ca/>**  

###  Information we gather

The following information is gathered from our website visitors:  
  
We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.  
  
This blog uses http://feedjit.com/ and http://www.google.com/analytics/ in order to track how many page views this site receives along with information such as language, country, city, web browser, operating system etc. However, this information is completely anonymous and DOES NOT identify you personally in any way.  

###  How we use the information we gather

We use the information to enhance your visitor experience.   
  
To process transactions  
  
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. If you win a giveaway your name and email will be given to the sponsor to facilitate delivery of prize.  
  
To send periodic emails  
  
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  
  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  

###  The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is accessible by myself, Jennifer Saarinen, owner of Homeschooling Mom 4 Two.  

###  Our use of cookies

This website and sponsor/affiliate adds that appear on this site may make use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.  
  
Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalize your experience of our website.  
  
Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.  
  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.  
  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.  
  
Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
  
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
If change are made to this Privacy Policy the date at the top of the page will be adjusted to reflect the adjusted date.  
  
**Your Consent  **  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy
